sup everyone 1005 who have a very
special video today and you're not
completely how cool this year this you
guys know how like that pancake place
like Denny's with me they made like a
Sonic Underground Sonic and Knuckles
plus well I always thought damn you know
what sucks balls
they all know other sock Underground
characters as plushies and so I
thought I make it myself this is the
plushie I made it is of Knuckles the
Echidna now there is a Knuckles the
Echidna plushie already it already
exists made by day the I do not
have it and you guys are probably
wondering actually you are wondering why
do I have the Knuckles the Echidna
Danny's plush toy well that's an easy
question I always thought I'm
not buying that
unless it's mint condition you healing
me I am I want up by sucking on product
if it is in good condition if he is in
great condition or bad condition I'll
only buy it is in mint condition there
is a reason this song cause I have this
all my life since I was like a
baby and and it is as clean as
since I first bought it I mean am I
wrong no I'm not wrong so as you can see
I made ain't no kickin applause I made
it myself it cut like eight hundred and
six bucks or some because I'm not
buying some cheap-ass fabric that some
got probably wiped his ass with at Home
Depot I am using the best
yeah customer like a hundred six buzzing
the red one alone it was like in
like a roll of like three feet and
so is all that as you can see I
made his hair
he doesn't have gloves or shoes yet
because I'm a makeup yet I was so
excited so I wanna show and if you
turn it
you can see like his tail and that
took me like eight hours to make but it
was worth it turned out like perfect and
so yeah now as I'll talk about the
other care like cussing I made
Knuckles because I thought I needed one
that I could like make easily and it was
perfect so I'll probably I know I'm
making other characters I'm not gonna
make Barbie and I was a big fat ass I'm
gonna make Manic I'm gonna make uncle
Chuck and coiling and Mindy and all
the good I mean mmm
you just can't beat the stock meanies
gonna have big tits
damn what the that
you guys know I mean peace
out everyone oh no no actually no not
peace out you got stay right here
you don't leave till I tell you to
this our talk well Gary
chalk the voice actor sock around he
apparently he he was in the trailer for
the live actors like that has like movie
in the background as an easter egg what
the are you doing Gary chop he
betrayed us he is in a movie
therefore modern Sonic what